Sir
سيد
There's news from the Court of Judicial Review
هناك أخبار من محكمة المراجعة القضائية
You may depart now
قد تغادر الآن
There's ash
هناك رماد
Since you can't do anything right,
بما أنه لا يمكنك فعل أي شيء بشكل صحيح ،
then you deserve to die.
ثم تستحق أن تموت.
Master
يتقن
There's no one here now.
لا يوجد أحد هنا الآن.
Hurry up and tell me.
أسرع وأخبرني.
Who is the person behind you?
من هو الشخص الذي يقف خلفك؟
Are you looking for me?
هل تبحث عني؟
You betrayed me, the Dark Emperor. Prepare to die.
لقد خانتني ، الإمبراطور المظلم. استعد للموت.
Who is this?
من هذا؟
This move is called "Luring the enemy into the trap."
وتسمى هذه الخطوة "جذب العدو في الفخ".
Although your martial arts are strong,
على الرغم من أن فنون القتال قوية ،
you're not very smart.
أنت لست ذكيا جدا.
Fine, fine.
بخير ، بخير.
What a clever trap.
يا له من فخ ذكي.
But you alone can't stop me.
لكنك وحدك لا تستطيع أن تمنعني.
What if you add me to the mix?
ماذا لو قمت بإضافتي إلى المزيج؟
Don't hold me back.
لا تعيقني.
Still not surrendering?
ما زلت لا تستسلم؟
So what do you suggest?
إذن ماذا تقترح؟
Do you remember the waiter and Old Li who were poisoned?
هل تتذكر النادل ولي القديم الذين تسمم؟
After the waiter died,
بعد وفاة النادل ،
we detained the prison guard who gave him water.
لقد احتجزنا حارس السجن الذي أعطاه الماء.
We also investigated
نحن أيضا التحقيق
Old Li, who had always delivered water to the Dali Court.
لي القديم ، الذي كان يسلم دائمًا المياه إلى محكمة الدالي.
Old Li is dead, right?
لي القديم ميت ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
It was my negligence.
كان إهمالي.
After that incident,
بعد هذا الحادث ،
I secretly conducted an internal investigation.
لقد أجريت سراً تحقيقًا داخليًا.
I actually found someone.
لقد وجدت شخصًا ما بالفعل.
But I haven't acted against him yet.
لكنني لم أتصرف ضده بعد.
As for the leader's conditions,
أما لظروف القائد ،
just agree to them.
فقط أوافق عليهم.
As long as they don't violate the law or morals,
طالما أنهم لا ينتهكون القانون أو الأخلاق ،
I can handle it.
يمكنني التعامل معها.
Whether he talks or not doesn't matter.
سواء كان يتحدث أم لا يهم.
We just need to make the person behind the scenes
نحتاج فقط إلى جعل الشخص وراء الكواليس
believe that he has talked.
نعتقد أنه تحدث.
Listen,
يستمع،
I'll tell you everything I know.
سأخبرك بكل ما أعرفه.
Shut up.
اسكت.
No talking.
لا يتحدث.
You dare act so arrogant even in the dungeon?
هل تجرؤ على التصرف المتعجرف حتى في الزنزانة؟
If you say one more word,
إذا قلت كلمة أخرى ،
you'll be flogged.
سوف يتم جلود.
Lord Hu,
اللورد هو ،
you've anticipated everything.
لقد توقعت كل شيء.
But there's one thing you didn't expect.
ولكن هناك شيء واحد لم تتوقعه.
You didn't expect that you're even dumber than we thought.
لم تكن تتوقع أنك حتى غباء مما كنا نظن.
You didn't anticipate my martial arts.
أنت لم تتوقع فنون القتال الخاصة بي.
Such shameless boasting.
مثل هذا التفاخر وقح.
Chunyang Sword
سيف تشونيانغ
It really is a fine sword.
انها حقا سيف جيد.
It truly lives up to its reputation.
انها حقا ترقى إلى مستوى سمعتها.
The original owner of this sword
المالك الأصلي لهذا السيف
asked me to use this sword
طلب مني استخدام هذا السيف
to slay you, the main culprit.
لذبحك ، الجاني الرئيسي.
Keep dreaming.
استمر في الحلم.
You’re asking for death.
أنت تطلب الموت.
You have nowhere left to run.
لم يتبق لك أي مكان للركض.
Why don’t you just surrender?
لماذا لا تستسلم فقط؟
I, the Underworld Emperor, am one of the Five Emperors.
أنا ، الإمبراطور السفلي ، أنا واحد من الأباطرة الخمسة.
How could I let myself be captured by you so easily?
كيف يمكنني أن أسمح لنفسي بالاستيلاء عليها بسهولة؟
And let you torture me?
ودعك تعذبني؟
Do you recognize him?
هل تعرفه؟
No, I don’t.
لا أنا لا.
Zeng Sheng.
Zeng Sheng.
Here.
هنا.
Go check the wanted notices from the Dali Court.
اذهب تحقق من الإشعارات المطلوبة من محكمة الدالي.
See if any match this face.
معرفة ما إذا كان أي تطابق هذا الوجه.
Yes, sir.
نعم يا سيدي.
Do you think this is too easy?
هل تعتقد أن هذا سهل للغاية؟
The Five Emperors.
الأباطرة الخمسة.
They are chosen from the major martial arts sects
تم اختيارهم من طوائف فنون القتال الكبرى
based on their martial arts skills.
بناء على مهاراتهم في فنون القتال.
As the Fox Emperor,
كإمبراطور الثعلب ،
I rank last among the Five Emperors.
أنا المرتبة الأخيرة بين الأباطرة الخمسة.
The Underworld Emperor is ranked fourth.
يحتل الإمبراطور السفلي المرتبة الرابعة.
When I fought him just now,
عندما قاتلته الآن ،
although his martial arts aren’t bad,
على الرغم من أن فنون القتال ليست سيئة ،
to call him the fourth best today
لدعوته رابع أفضل اليوم
seems a bit of a stretch.
يبدو قليلا من امتداد.
Of course,
بالطبع،
this is all just my own speculation.
هذا كل شيء مجرد تكهنات بلدي.
Sir,
سيد،
what should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
All our leads have dried up.
لقد جفت جميع خيوطنا.
Your master is already dead.
سيدك قد مات بالفعل.
You can talk now, can’t you?
يمكنك التحدث الآن ، أليس كذلك؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll tell you everything I know.
سأخبرك بكل ما أعرفه.
I'll tell you all of it.
سأخبركم كل ذلك.
Seven years ago,
قبل سبع سنوات ،
it was Lord Mingdi
كان اللورد مينغدي
who saved me from a pile of corpses.
الذي أنقذني من كومة من الجثث.
After that,
بعد ذلك،
he sent me to the Western Regions to recover.
أرسلني إلى المناطق الغربية للتعافي.
Until the year before last,
حتى العام السابق الماضي ،
he summoned me back.
استدعى لي.
He said he had an important task for me.
قال إنه كان لديه مهمة مهمة بالنسبة لي.
So,
لذا،
you came to Shendu
أتيت إلى شيندو
and established the Blood God Sect.
وأنشأت طائفة الله.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
At first,
في البداية،
we just recited scriptures
قمنا فقط بتلاوة الكتب المقدسة
and discussed teachings.
وناقش التعاليم.
Until two months ago,
حتى قبل شهرين ،
Lord Mingdi suddenly summoned me
اللورد مينغدي استدعائي فجأة
and said we needed the blood of young women
وقال إننا بحاجة إلى دم الشابات
for a ritual.
لطقوس.
After that, you all know what happened.
بعد ذلك ، تعرفون جميعًا ما حدث.
Our Blood God Sect killed people and drained their blood,
لقد قتل طائفة إلهنا من دماء الناس واستنزاف دمائهم ،
spreading fear.
نشر الخوف.
Earlier, you said
في وقت سابق ، قلت
the massacre at General Li Zuo's residence
المذبحة في إقامة الجنرال لي زو
was orchestrated by someone in the court.
تم تنظيمه من قبل شخص ما في المحكمة.
Who exactly is this person?
من هو بالضبط هذا الشخص؟
All I know is
كل ما أعرفه هو
that person now holds a high position.
يحمل هذا الشخص الآن وضعًا كبيرًا.
But as for who it is,
ولكن بالنسبة لمن هو ،
I'm not sure.
لست متأكدًا.
Back then in Shuangyue, I was just a low-level thug.
في ذلك الوقت في Shuangyue ، كنت مجرد سفاح منخفض المستوى.
I followed the leader
تابعت القائد
and committed many hired killings.
وارتكب العديد من عمليات القتل المستأجر.
In the end, we turned on each other.
في النهاية ، تحولنا على بعضنا البعض.
Most of us were killed or wounded.
قُتل معظمنا أو جرحه.
I suppose it was retribution.
أفترض أنه كان الانتقام.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I've said everything I needed to say.
لقد قلت كل ما أحتاجه لقوله.
I only ask for a quick death.
أنا فقط أطلب الموت السريع.
That's not difficult.
هذا ليس صعبًا.
But—
لكن-
If you want your body to remain intact after death,
إذا كنت تريد أن يظل جسمك سليما بعد الموت ،
and not be thrown into the wild for stray dogs to devour,
ولا يتم إلقاؤه في البرية حتى تلتهم الكلاب الضالة ،
you must agree to one thing.
يجب أن توافق على شيء واحد.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Hand over the antidote for the blood poison.
تسليم الترياق لسم الدم.
The third brother is dead.
الأخ الثالث مات.
There's that old fox Hu Zhengyi in the Dali Court.
هناك هذا الثعلب القديم هو Zhengyi في محكمة الدالي.
It's not so easy to get in and kill someone.
ليس من السهل الوصول إلى شخص ما وقتلهم.
But the third brother's death wasn't in vain.
لكن وفاة الأخ الثالث لم تكن سدى.
The Phoenix case caused such a huge stir.
تسببت قضية فينيكس في ضجة كبيرة.
And now the Blood God Sect is involved too.
والآن تشارك طائفة الله في الدم أيضًا.
I'm afraid that without sacrificing a "Shadow,"
أخشى أنه دون التضحية بـ "الظل" ،
it would be hard to answer for this.
سيكون من الصعب الإجابة على هذا.
Hu Zhengyi.
هو Zhengyi.
The Blood God case is just being wrapped up so hastily.
قضية إله الدم يتم اختتامها على عجل.
Brother Jianxing,
الأخ جيانكينغ ،
it seems you've recovered well.
يبدو أنك تعافيت بشكل جيد.
Lord Hu,
اللورد هو ،
you helped me get the antidote for the blood poison.
لقد ساعدتني في الحصول على ترياق لسم الدم.
I owe you for that.
أنا مدين لك بذلك.
But this case—
لكن هذه الحالة -
is it really ending so hastily?
هل هو حقا ينتهي على عجل؟
And you're even posting notices outside to announce it to the world.
وأنت حتى تنشر إشعارات في الخارج للإعلان عن العالم.
I'm sorry, but I can't agree with this.
أنا آسف ، لكن لا يمكنني الموافقة على هذا.
The Blood God Sect has been destroyed.
تم تدمير طائفة الله.
The sect leader, as the main culprit,
زعيم الطائفة ، باعتباره الجاني الرئيسي ،
has also been sentenced to immediate execution.
كما حُكم عليه بالإعدام الفوري.
Why can't the case be closed?
لماذا لا يمكن إغلاق القضية؟
How is that considered hasty?
كيف يعتبر ذلك متسرع؟
But you know in your heart,
لكنك تعرف في قلبك ،
there's still someone behind all this.
لا يزال هناك شخص ما وراء كل هذا.